Register of the Pasternak Family Papers, 1877-2012
Hoover Institution Archives
- PASTERNAK TRUST ARCHIVES, 1877-2012; 118.0 boxes
  - AUDIOVISUAL MATERIAL, 1910-2011 (Box 177-178)
    - Sound recordings, 1958-2010 and undated (Boxes 177-178)
      - "Poetry of Boris Pasternak," lecture by Lydia Pasternak Slater. 1 sound tape reel, undated (Box 178)
      - "Rosa Pasternak Plays Bach," 1 sound tape reel and 2 sound shellac discs, circa 1930s
      - "Rosalia plays Schumann," 1 sound shellac disc, undated
      - "Rosalia Kaufman igraet Bakha," 1 sound tape reel, circa 1930s
      - Rosalia Kaufman plays Bach and Schumann, 1 sound disc (CD), 1933 (Box 177)
      - "Shaken Harmony," 2 sound tape reels, 1982
        Talk about and piano music by Boris Pasternak produced by Canadian Broadcasting Corporation.
      - Vil'iam Shekspir v perevodakh S. Marshaka i B. Pasternaka: chitaiut avtory perevodov, 1 sound vinyl disc, 1976
      - Unidentified, 8 sound tape reels, 1 sound shellac disc, and 1 sound dictation disc, undated (Boxes 177-178)
    - Videorecordings, 1983-2011 and undated
      - Art of Leonid Pasternak, 16 mm motion picture film, undated (Film shelf shelf)
      - "Family Potrait: The Pasternaks," 1 video disc (DVD), undated (Box 177)
      - Kontraste: Pasternak, 1 video cassette (VHS), 1983 (Box 177)
      - Nobel Jubilee, 1 video cassette (VHS), 1991 (Box 177)
      - Pasternak, 1 video cassette (VHS), undated (Box 177)
      - Pasternak Exhibition, 1 video cassette (VHS), 1988 (Box 177)
      - Pasternak Film, 1 video cassette (VHS), 2000 (Box 177)
      - Pasternak v Rossii i Germanii, 1 video cassette (VHS), 2001 (Box 177)
      - Russian Impressionist: Paintings and Drawings by Leonid Pasternak, 1890-1945, 1 video cassette (Betamax), undated (Box 177)
      - Zhazhda poiska. Quest, with Charles Pasternak, 1 video disc (DVD), 2011 (Box 177)